ILR School Metropolitan District Office Additional Files /4089
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Metropolitan District Office Additional Files
1953-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4089
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3086211
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3012: Alice Cook Papers /3019: ILR School Metropolitan District Selected Documents /3072 PUBS: ILR School Miscellaneous Publications of the School /4004: ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4068: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office, Anne Nelson Papers /4080: Betty Lall Files /4257: ILR School Metropolitan District Selected Files /4266m: ILR School Metropolitan District Levi Strauss files /4277: ILR School Metropolitan District Trade Union Health Education Project Papers /4291: Martin P. Catherwood Library Philip R. Dankert Files /4296: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Manuals /4296 AV: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Audio-Visual Materials
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Metropolitan District Office.
3086211
- LMRDA Regulations and Interpretative Bulletins; Election of Officers of Labor Organizations; Electing Union Officials, An Introductory Course in Teaching and Training Methods for Management Development; Revised Report "Trends and Developments in Extension (Box 1)
  - LMRDA Regulations and Interpretative Bulletins, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Election of Officers of Labor Organizations, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Scope and Contents
    Bound
  - Electing Union Officers, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - An Introductory Course in - Teaching and Training Methods for Management Development, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Revised Report "Trends and Developments in Extension Program", 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A Dialogue on Comparable Worth, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Women Workers - Foreword by Helvi Sipila, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lifelong Learning - Teaching Writing, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ongoing Partners in Equality Network (TC-3), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Oral History Project, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - New Projects, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Mineworkers Exchange, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Risley, Robert, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Metro Manpower Project, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minority Arbitration Development Programs (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - National Assoc. of Stat Univ. and Land Grant Coll., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Memos to and from Dean McKersie, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - File Ithaca, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Labor Studies Universally Undergraduate Program Announcements, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Manpower Project-USDOL-New Contract, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ten Year Objectives of the Metropolitan Center; NYSSILR Cornell University, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Grant Budgets, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Trade Union Health Education Project Report 1972-74, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Trade Union Health Education 1972-74, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Health Proposal -1974-75, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Extension Proposals to ILR Research; OSHA Miscellaneous Correspondence; Opera Labor Relations; Labor Advisory Council; Labor Advisory Committee Minutes, 3/80; Labor Advisory Committee Meeting, Spring, 1982; Labor College and LLA; Labor Legislative Repre (Box 2)
  - Extension Proposals to ILR Research, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - OSHA - Misc. Correspondence, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Opera Labor Relations, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Labor Advisory Council, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Labor Advisory Committee Minutes 3/80, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Labor Advisory Committee Meeting - Spring 1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Labor College + LCA, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Labor Legislative Representatives, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Labor Education Advisory Network/Serv. (Lean - Leas), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Labor Advisory Committee, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Lois 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Kaufman Correspondence, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - National Council of Negro Women, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Proposal - OSHA, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Railroad Proposal/Kaufman, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Labor College, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Labor-Management Committee, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Budget - OSHA, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Webs - A Career and Educational Counseling Service (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence, February, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence, January, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence, December 1974 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence, November 1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence - October 1974 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence - September 1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Puerto Rican Labor Dept. Project, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - McKersie Review - MLR - 1972 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Puerto Rican BLS Conference, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Articles on Swedish Exchange Workers at Saab-Scania, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Original Copies of Articles, Newsletters, etc. for Workers Exchange (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Worker Exchange Program November, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Candidates in Exchange Project, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence - January 1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Voc. Ed., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Synopsis of Work and Education Conference NYC 12/17/76; Graduate Study Leading to the Degree of Master of Arts in Labor Studies Proposal to Rutgers University; Industrial Relations Degree Programs Offered at Colleges and Universities in the US and Can (Box 3)
  - Sources of Funds for Labor Education, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1976 - Women's Project (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Copies of Budgets, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Workers Exchange Program Correspondence - August 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence, February, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence - December and January, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Work Experiments and Improving the Quality of Work Life in the United States, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence March, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence, March 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence, April, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence, May 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Worker Exchange Program Correspondence, June, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Proposal for a Worker Exchange Project (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Barbados Labor School, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - B.M. Kapur, Visit of, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chilean Correspondence, 1963-1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Pedro Guglielmetti, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - International Correspondence (Lois Gray General), 1961 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Lois Gray Correspondence - Orit, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Annual Report; International Projects Lois Gray general; Candidates for Sloan Coordination; Sloan Grant Labor 2000; Lois Gray Correspondence Emilio Morgado; Homer La Rue Correspondence; Sloan Grant course material; Alfred P. Sloan Foundation; UAW (Box 4)
  - International Projects (Lois Gray General), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Jack (Candidates for Sloan Coord.), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Sloan Grant (Labor 2000), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Latin American Labor Education Projects, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Lois Gray - Correspondence--Emilio Morgado, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Lois Gray, 1978-1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sloan Grant (Course Material), 1953-1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - UAW Seminar on International Affairs, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Worker Education Conference, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Kaufman, Jacob J., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Worker Exchange Program Copies of Forms, Proposal, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Gray, Lois, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- University of Puerto Rico Correspondence Lois Gray; Lois Gray Correspondence 1981; Lois Gray Chron file 3/79; Staff Biographical Information; Lois Gray Sent Correspondence, 1981; Lois Gray Correspondence; Caribbean Seminar; Chilean Seminar Announc (Box 5)
  - University of Puerto Rico Correspondence (Lois Gray- Puerto Rico), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Lois Gray Correspondence 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - LG - Chron File 3/79-, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Staff Biographical Information, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Gray, Lois - Gen'l Corres. 1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Lois - 1981 (Sent) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Gray Correspondence, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Caribbean Seminar Arrangements, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Univ. of Puerto Rico-Inst. Lr Reports, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Trade Union Development -and- Trade Union Education, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Caribbean Trade Unionist, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Trade Union Development -and- Trade Union Education in the British Caribbean, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Trade Unions and Politics in the British Caribbean, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 13)